GREG STRIDER

Native Brazilian Translator & Localization Specialist 3+ years of experience

Summary

Over 3 years of experience in translation/localization. English > Portuguese | Spanish > Portuguese

Main fields of expertise: IT, video games and apps, marketing Looking for new projects and long-term collaborations. Weekends availability.

Website/portfolio: http://gregstrider.com | Email: gboufleur@gmail.com

ProZ: https://www.proz.com/profile/2502305 | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gregstrider/

Work Experience

Valve Corporation (Nov 2015 - present)

Steam Translation Server – Community Moderator (Brazilian Portuguese)

Localizing Steam, the global leader in online game distribution, (desktop/mobile clients, website and other services, e.g. Big Picture and SteamVR) and Valve games (e.g. Dota 2, Counter-Strike: Global Offensive, Team Fortress 2) from English into Brazilian Portuguese and proofreading translations.

Freelance Translator (Jan 2015 – present)

Working as a freelance translator from English and Spanish into Brazilian Portuguese, specializing in IT and marketing texts, as well as video games and apps localization. I have experience as a service provider for both translation agencies and direct clients. Portfolio: http://gregstrider.com/#portfolio

Volunteer Experience

Translators without Borders (Mar 2018 – now)

Working as a volunteer translator for Translator without Borders, a non-profit organization that works with thousands of volunteers to provide vital information to people in need, in their language.

Languages

Brazilian Portuguese (Native) English (Proficiency) Spanish (Advanced)

Education

Assessed with C2 Level in English Proficiency (EF SET) Associate's degree in Information Technology, ULBRA Cristo Redentor, 2015 — 2018



